takemylinks.com 2011-01-04

# P6L.ORG - Privacy Policy

**1\. Introduction:**

**1.1. This privacy policy has been written to clearly show our commitment to our visitors privacy. The following lines reveals the ways by which  [ p6l.org](http://p6l.org/) collects and uses information**

**2.1. [ p6l.org](http://p6l.org/) collects visitors information in 2 ways:**

**a. Automatically collected information by the hosting Web Server, like all Internet sites  
b. Links provided voluntarily by the visitors through site's forms.**  
  
---  
  
**2\. Automatically Collected Information:**

**2.1. Internet WebServer automatically records some visitors information. These include the time and date of the visit, the IP of the visitor, the name of the Internet browser, the operating system, the country , the referrer URL.**  
  
**3\. Forms:**

**3.1. The information we are voluntarily given through various site forms allow us help our visitors by providing valuable information and contacting them. In the same time, it helps us improve the site content to fit the needs of our visitors. **

**3.2. Under no circumstances, except via judicial subpoena, shall these information be presented or sold to a third party, whether advertisers, funding sources, or otherwise. It is possible to provide advertisers with summarized statistical information, in aggregate form, through which there is absolutely no way to reveal the identity of our visitors. No personally identifiable information will be given to a third party whatsoever, under any condition, and this includes, without limitation, advertisers and funding sources.**  
  
**4\. External Links:**

**4.1. This site contains links to external sites. [ p6l.org](http://p6l.org/) is not responsible for the privacy policy practiced in these sites nor its content. **

**4.2. This site contains links to sites the offer tracking services. [ p6l.org](http://p6l.org/) is not responsible for the privacy policy of these sites, and has no control over the way in which these site will (are) use (ing) the collected information. **

**By visiting and using our site consent the right of [ p6l.org](http://p6l.org/) to use the services of such sites, and in the same time holds it free from the responsibility of tracking sites deeds.**  
  
**5\. Information Security:**

**5.1.[p6l.org](http://p6l.org/) provides for information security measures against loss, abuse, or content modification . This is assured through the fact that only few authorized and trusted persons are dealing with these information. Regular backup copies are made and saved in a safe place.**  
  
**6\. Modification of Information:**

**6.1. You can email us to modify any information.[Contact info can be found here](http://p6l.org/contactus.html)**  
  
**7\. Contacting the site:**

**7.1. Use the "[Contact us](http://p6l.org/contactus.html)" page.**
